Guide to the Consolidation Coal Company Records, 1854-1971 AIS.2011.03
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Secretary's Contract Files, VI.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Carnegie Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), May 24-October 28, 1916; 1812.
  - Louisville & Nashville RR Co. and Camden Coal Co., May 14, 1910; 1813.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and McClane Mining Co., February 21, 1916; 1814.
  - Jacob E. Ridgeway Plan, June 1-June 21, 1916; 1824.
  - Jefferson Safe Deposit Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Illinois, June 9, 1916; 1826.
  - Duquesne Light Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 1, 1916; 1828.
  - R. L. Aubrey and The Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co., September 15, 1915; 1829.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Peters Creek Gas Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), August 11, 1916-October 1, 1935; 1830.
  - Central Youghipgheny Coal Co., July 31, 1916-September 16, 1925; 1832.
  - Florence Brown et al, September 29, 1916; 1833.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Illinois and Montour Coal Co., August 18, 1916; 1834.
  - The New Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Blue Jay Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), August 25, 1916; 1835.
  - West Memphis Packet Co. and The Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Tennessee), May 12, 1916; 1840.
  - William J. Bunn and Fidelity & Deposit Co., September 18, 1916; 1841.
  - Pittsburgh Coal & Coke Co., December 5, 1916; 1851.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Charlerois Poster Advertising Co., November 1, 1916-November 4, 1933; 1855.
  - Louisa Campbell, September 27, 1916-January 7, 1917; 1860.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Emery Gates, September 11, 1916; 1861.
  - The Fayette City Real Estate & Improvement Co., January 10, 1917; 1862.
  - George E. Adams, December 6, 1916; 1863.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Pittsburgh Porter Advertising Co., February 1, 1917; 1870.
  - War Department, US and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Kentucky), December 16, 1916; 1871.
  - The Chicago & Alton RR Co. and Montour Coal Co., February 1, 1911; 1872.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 21, 1917-March 22, 1922; 1873-1.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 22, 1933-March 24, 1937; 1873-4.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 28, 1923-March 28, 1928; 1873-2.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 27, 1929-March 23, 1932; 1873-3.
  - Huntington Sand & Gravel Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 1, 1917; 1878.
  - Montour Coal Co. and Royal Collieries Co., January 8, 1917; 1879.
  - South Pittsburgh Coal & Supply Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., December 19, 1916; 1880.
  - The Majestic Co. and The New Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 20, 1917-February 25, 1919; 1881.
  - The Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co. and The Union Trust Co. of Pittsburgh, January 1, 1902-March 28, 1917; 1882.
  - Pittsburgh & Erie Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 12, 1917; 1883.
  - James Wilson et ux and Pittsburgh Coal Co., November 17, 1916; 1884.
  - Ethan Stone and Cincinnati Fuel Co., July 1, 1847; 1885.
  - Guy Brown (Gillespie Coal Co.)(Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), January 10-April 25, 1917; 1886.
  - The Chicago & Alton RR Co. and Montour Coal Co. (Illinois Collieries Co.), November 8, 1920; 1887.
  - Commissioners of Highways of Auburn Twp. and Commissioners of Highways of Virden Twp., Illinois, February 24, 1916; 1888.
  - H. C. Frick Coke Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, June 8, 1911-March 21, 1945; 1889. (Box 62)
  - Joseph S. Elliott and Robert C. Campbell, September 14, 1892; 1891.
  - The Monongahela River Consolidated Coal & Coke Co., Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Steel Co., June 6, 1905-March 23, 1917; 1892.
  - Wabash Railway Co. and Montour Coal Co., August 23, 1906; 1894.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Meadowlands Coal Co., March 22, 1917; 1895.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Angelo Micolo, March 1, 1917; 1896.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John Teyssier, December 1, 1916; 1897.
  - J. W. Emery and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 24-June 9, 1917; 1902.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Gratza Wozlich, April 24, 1917; 1903.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Emily Dineley, May 5, 1917; 1904.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Samuel Johnson, May 12, 1917; 1905.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 29, 1917; 1908.
  - Thomas Lowry, trustee, May 20, 1903-October 28, 1904; 1910 A-L.
  - Thomas Lowry, trustee, May 8, 1903-March 30, 1904; 1910 M-Z.
  - City of Litchfield, IL and Carbon Coal & Manufacturing Co. (assigned to Girard Coal Co.), March 24, 1894; 1912.
  - James Lorton and Chicago -Virden Coal Co., July 20, 1893; 1913.
  - Judson T. Williams and Sorento Coal Co., April 1, 1904; 1914.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Irwin Smith, July 11, 1917; 1916.
  - Pennsylvania Savings Fund & Loan Association with Mercantile Trust Co., Surety and Pennsylvania Mining Co., June 28, 1901-July 16, 1917; 1917.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Keystone Steel & Wire Co., June 29, 1917; 1918.
  - Buenos Aires, Argentine Republic, June 25, 1915-February 28, 1925; 1920.
  - Sinking Fund, Louisville KY and O=Donnell & Co., December 30, 1919; 1928.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and United Coal Corporation, July 25, 1917; 1929.
  - Marie H. Snodgrass and Pittsburgh Coal Land Co., September 5, 1917; 1932.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Clark Ayres et ux, June 23, 1917; 1934.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Thomas W. Welfer, September 5, 1917; 1935.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. (NJ) and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Pennsylvania, December 31, 1913-July 29, 1914; 1936.
  - H. F. Stark and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 24, 1917; 1939.
  - Montour Coal Co. and N. E. Burton & Herman Schultz, September 8, 1917; 1940.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Fernand Saut, August 10, 1917; 1941.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Will Gravese, May 12, 1917; 1942.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Pleasant Brooks, July 2, 1917; 1943.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Minnesota By-Product Coke Co., February 1, 1917; 1945.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Seaboard By-Product Coke Co., February 1, 1917; 1946.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. (KY) and Morris & George Klempner, August 1-September 1, 1917; 1951.
  - Kanawha & Michigan Railway Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (WVA), October 11, 1917; 1954.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Mike Cherevka et ux, May 1, 1917; 1956.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Ono Kemp, April 5, 1917; 1959.
  - The Chicago-Virden Coal Co. and The Equitable Trust Co.(assigned to First Trust & Savings Bank), September 19, 1901; 1961.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William Henderson et ux., April 5, 1917; 1962.
  - Pennsylvania Water Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Land Co., April 30, 1916; 1964.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Inland Steel Co., March 24, 1915-February 15, 1917; 1965.
  - Montour Coal Co. and Joseph Hann & S. H. Cummins, November 26, 1917; 1966.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Percy Thompson et ux., April 5, 1917-October 24, 1923; 1967.
  - Sarah Feree et al. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., February 7, 1916; 1968.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Montour Coal Co., December 11, 1917; 1969. (Box 63)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. A. Barnum, May 23, 1917-May 22, 1918; 1978.
  - Montour Coal Co. and John E. Sankey, March 1, 1918; 1982.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and L. P. Carter, July 30, 1918; 1983.
  - The Springfield Coal Mining & Tile Co., February 19, 1885; 1986.
  - Climax Trading Co., November 23, 1894; 1987.
  - Girard Coal Co., September 1, 1904-November 2, 1905; 1988 A-G.
  - Girard Coal Co., February 1, 1904-June 11, 1906; 1988 H-Z.
  - Litchfield Mining & Power Co., September 10, 1878-October 20, 1904; 1989 A-H.
  - Litchfield Mining & Power Co., March 17, 1900-June 25, 1904; 1989 J-Z.
  - Chicago-Virden Coal Co., March 22, 1893-September 1, 1908; 1990.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Mike Pucher, February 20, 1918; 1994.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Thomas Rollins assigned to Mitchell Evans, March 30, 1918; 1995.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Rush Coal Co., May 22, 1918; 1999.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and National Tube Co., January 23-May 22, 1918; 2000.
  - Henry A. Matthews et ux and Pittsburgh Coal Co., June 1, 1918; 2002.
  - Richard J. Green Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 14, 1918; 2003.
  - V. E. Griffin, May 6, 1918; 2004.
  - William Seaman and Maryland Casualty Co., May 28, 1918; 2005.
  - Citizens Sand & Gravel Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 1, 1918; 2007.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Karl Staub, July 24, 1918; 2009.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Arthur Lee, July 24, 1918; 2010.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William F. Sossong, August 5, 1918; 2011.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and F. M. Wallace, April 24, 1918; 2017.
  - M. A. Ford, Adm of James L. McDade Estate, October 8, 1918; 2021.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Wendelin Shallenberger, October 9, 1918; 2023.
  - R. M. Cross et al. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), August 30, 1918-April 25, 1924; 2024. (Box 64)
  - Montour Coal Co. and The Ridge Coal Mining Co., August 6, 1918; 2025.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co., May 29, 1918-June 18, 1924; 2026.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and McClinton Marshall Co & Hughes-Foulkrod Co., September 30-October 10, 1918; 2027.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Abraham L. Bowden, October 21, 1918; 2031.
  - R. Vernon Clark, Trustee (Southern Coal, Coke & Mining Co.), November 25, 1918-October 6, 1919; 2033.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Stefan Guro, John Petranski, John W. Price and John Yahaviczkj et ux, November 25, 1918; 2036.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Carnegie Land Co., December 18, 1918; 2038.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Elia Profio, December 18, 1918; 2039.
  - Thomas Harper, November 1, 1918; 2041.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Grover C. Keibler, November 26, 1918; 2042.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William Opfer, December 18, 1918; 2045.
  - Sarah Harriet Stewart et al and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 1, 1918; 2047.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and C. W. Bromley, December 30, 1918; 2049.
  - Isaac N. Hagan and Monga Land Co., February 5, 1919; 2050.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and John Puckey, February 5, 1919; 2051.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Sylvester Selva, March 3, 1919-July 28, 1920; 2055.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co, Pittsburgh Coal Land Co., and Albert C. Fulton et ux, February 26, 1919; 2057.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William E. Carothers, February 4, 1919; 2059.
  - Elizabeth S. Moore and The Peoples Natural Gas Co., January 18, 1904; 2060.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and H. C. Frick Coke Co., February 7, 1916; 2061.
  - Trustees Pittsburgh Division #52 Order of RR Telegraphers, January 20, 1919; 2062.
  - W. P. Simmons, Attorney for George Seiboll heirs and Peoples Natural Gas Co., December 2, 1915-January 8, 1921; 2063.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Frances and Charles Caucci, April 23, 1919; 2064.
  - Westmoreland Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 24, 1919; 2065.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Valentine Gaspari, May 28, 1919; 2067.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and W. V. Pearson, Jr., July 23, 1919; 2068.
  - Horacio D. Harilaos, agent and The Pittsburgh Coal Co., May 26-July 1, 1919; 2070.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and John Haas, June 25, 1919; 2072.
  - South Pittsburgh Water Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., April 17, 1919; 2073.
  - John W. Donnan and Pittsburgh Coal Co., July 31, 1919; 2080.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Saunders C. Bennett, September 24, 1919; 2081.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Edward Perkins, June 23, 1919; 2082.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William E. Coughenour, Jr., September 24, 1919; 2083.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William E. Coughenour, October 7-December 19, 1919; 2084.
  - Hoffmann Bros. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 14-September 1, 1919; 2085.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Robert E. Pangburn et ux, September 5, 1919; 2086.
  - South Pittsburgh Water Co. and Pittsburgh Water Co., September 3, 1919; 2087.
  - John G. Schafer and Emma Jane Snyder, August 13, 1919; 2088.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William Jacks & Co., August 22, 1916; 2091.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Joseph Lazzari, September 5, 1919-May 14, 1928; 2093.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Valentine Berger, August 7, 1919; 2097.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Frank Janoski et ux, October 8, 1919; 2098.
  - Charles M. Messmore et ux and Peter E. Sheppard assigned to Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 9, 1919; 2101.
  - Monga Land Co. and Phoebe Cook, August 15, 1919; 2103.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Michael Schreiner, December 3, 1919; 2105.
  - N. C. Morrison, agent and Pittsburgh Coal Land Co., October 16, 1919; 2106.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Daniel Spencer, et ux, November 11, 1919; 2112.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Pelevich, December 29, 1919; 2113.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and C. E. Lenhart et al, trustees of the estate of I.W. Semans, October 24-November 5, 1919; 2114.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. et al and Island Creek Coal Co., December 30, 1919; 2118.
  - Rock Run Fuel Gas Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 6, 1920; 2119.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Agnes Rank, February 25, 1920; 2121.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Patrick J. Mc Donough, March 24, 1920; 2123.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Newton D. Barker, US Secy of War-Inland Waterways Division, March 15, 1920; 2125.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Zeddie Perry, February 25, 1920; 2126.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William T. Horrell, February 6, 1920; 2129.
  - Eureka Coal Co., February 2, 1891; 2131. (Box 65)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Frank Joseph Harde et ux, April 28, 1920; 2135.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Nick Liticik, April 28, 1920; 2136.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and State of Illinois, April 19, 1920; 2142.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and C. M. Neeld, August 26, 1920; 2153.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Illinois Coal & Coke Co., July 29-September 1, 1920; 2174.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Louis Knaus et ux, July 28, 1920; 2181.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Frank Bennett, September 27, 1920; 2186.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and James Radcliff, September 27, 1920; 2187.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George S. Harrison, September 27, 1920; 2188.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Leon Berger, August 14, 1920; 2189.
  - Mary Gilchrist and Pittsburgh Coal Co., October 6, 1920; 2191.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Dravosburg Oil & Gas Co., November 8, 1920; 2192.
  - Noah D. Speer, September 24, 1920; 2193.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William M. Henderson assigned to Robert & Charles Griffith, September 30, 1920; 2195.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The New York Central Magazine, October 21, 1920; 2197.
  - South Pittsburgh Water Co., October 15, 1920; 2198.
  - Riter-Conley Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), October 26, 1920; 2199.
  - Melvin Mayfield, November 29, 1920; 2203.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Pasquale Desantis, October 6, 1920; 2204.
  - Monga Land Co. and Margaret S. Beachdel, November 23, 1920; 2205.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William D. Johnston, November 23, 1920; 2207.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Martin J. Downey, November 23, 1920; 2209.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Matthew Smith, November 23, 1920; 2210.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and R. Stacey Altman et ux & John W. Manown, January 8, 1920; 2216.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Bess-Etta Coal Co., August 16, 1920; 2218.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Duquesne Light Co., April 1, 1921; 2221.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Robert E. Galbraith, January 21, 1921; 2223.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and William Reeves, April 4, 1921; 2226.
  - William S. Schafer and Pittsburgh Coal Co., January 17, 1921; 2227.
  - Elizabeth S. Moore et al and Pittsburgh Coal Co., March 28, 1921; 2232.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph Tomn et ux, April 4, 1921; 2233.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Abraham & Frank Mains, May 25, 1921; 2239.
  - S. Eleanor Sawyer and Fidelity & Deposit Co. of MD, May 14, 1921; 2243.
  - Pennsylvania Coal Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Wisconsin et al, March 21, 1921-April 9, 1924; 2244.
  - Edgewood Country Club, June 16, 1921; 2245.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company and James Slaughterbeck, June 21, 1921; 2246.
  - Pittsburgh & Allegheny Telephone Company, July 1, 1921; 2252.
  - Bob-Lo Coal & Sales Corporation, August 9, 1921; 2253.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company & Martin Roback et ux., September 6, 1921; 2255.
  - Clifford Hackey et ux., September 6, 1921-January 21, 1924; 2256.
  - South Fayette Coal Company, July 23, 1920; 2264.
  - Eclipse Gas Coal Company (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), September 6, 1919; 2265.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company & John Archer et ux., November 28, 1921; 2266.
  - G. B. Bennett, October 5, 1921; 2267.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company & Joseph Crea et ux., November 7, 1921; 2268.
  - James A. Dunn et ux and John M. Dunn, August 29, 1919 - September 27, 1921; 2271.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company and Stephen Gascia, October 5, 1921; 2272.
  - Pierre J. Mortelette et ux, November 28, 1921; 2278.
  - Freehold Oil & Gas Company, October 10, 1921; 2279.
  - Lukes Knafelc, November 28, 1921; 2280.
  - James Radcliff, January 4, 1921-January 3, 1922; 2287.
  - The Broad-Third Realty Company, December 16, 1921-April 15, 1927; 2288.
  - S. J. Harry Company, December 29, 1921-January 10, 1922; 2290.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Company and Carl R Banner & Alex M. Borland, September 29, 1921-May 25, 1923; 2294.
  - Bell Telephone Co. of PA, February 8, 1922-March 3, 1927; 2295.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Corrado Gas Coal Co., October 21, 1921; 2299.
  - Consumers Fuel Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co./Virginville Fuel Co., January 25, 1922; 2300.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Constant Dowlain, et ux, June 7, 1922; 2302.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Thomas E. Evans & W.B. Lawton, Trustees of Evans Gas Coal Co., January 25, 1922; 2304.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Joseph Kuma, March 30, 1922; 2310.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and City of Pittsburgh, April 4, 1922; 2316.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Julius Perecko, January 25, 1922; 2317.
  - Luella Moore Robbins et al and Samuel R. Sorber, December 30, 1921-January 23, 1923; 2323.
  - W. A. Seifert, May 26, 1922; 2325. (Box 66)
  - Recorder of deeds of Washington Co., PA, April 4, 1922; 2334.
  - Michael Burin and Pittsburgh Coal Co, February 23, 1922; 2336.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co., Carnegie Coal Co. and Henderson Coal Co., July 20, 1922; 2337.
  - The R. G. Johnson Co. and Pittsburgh Coal Co., August 4, 1922; 2339.
  - Fairchaner Lumber Co., October 2, 1922; 2340.
  - John H. Donnan et al., August 16-31, 1920; 2342.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and John T. Price, October 11, 1922; 2348.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and F. J. L. Moyne, September 7, 1922-June 24, 1941; 2354.
  - Alexander Abraham and Abraham Staddard, October 6, 1922; 2361.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and William B. Scaife & Sons Co., October 31, 1922; 2370.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Lindley Coal Co., January 12-31, 1923; 2371.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John, James, Joseph and Frank Uzlik, February 1, 1923; 2374.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. J. Harry Co., October 23, 1922; 2376.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Delaware & Hudson Co., October 23, 1922; 2382.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Pennsylvania RR YMCA, Philadelphia, December 6, 1922; 2383.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Louis Petrilena et ux, March 26, 1923; 2384.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and The Athens Electric Co., Athens OH, & Hocking Power Co., November 29, 1922; 2387.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Joseph & Antoinette Rozman, November 13, 1922-May 21, 1923; 2394.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Henry A. Pfeifer, April 30, 1923-April 3, 1924; 2398.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank P. Mank, April 21-May 21, 1923; 2399.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Hillman Coal & Coke Co., May 1, 1923; 2402.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Edward Monaco, April 28, 1923; 2404.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and S. J. Harry Co., May 26, 1923; 2411.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and David J. Wright, January 1, 1923; 2414.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Fred Schafer, February 2, 1922; 2415.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Benjamin N. McCormick, June 24, 1921-July 8, 1925; 2417.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Henry Schuffert, May 16, 1923; 2418.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Ernest Pucher et ux, July 6, 1923; 2420.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Frederick J. Boulter et ux., July 6, 1923; 2427.
  - Athens Connecting Railway Co., May 25, 1912-August 9, 1923; 2434.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Land Co. and Joe and Palma Sartori, August 6, 1923; 2438.
  - Great Lakes Coal Mining Co., March 27, 1917-June 16, 1926; 2442. (Oversize 129)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Sunday Creek Coal Co. (Blueprint pulled to map case 1/7/7-8), April 1, 1920; 2447. (Box 66)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and First National Bank Building Co., Detroit MI, September 19, 1923; 2451.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Pittsburgh & Western Mining Co., October 24, 1923; 2452.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Harry K. Ullom, September 15, 1923; 2461.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Elmer J. Kurtz et ux, August 22, 1923; 2463.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Samuel W. Fennell et ux, October 24, 1923; 2467.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Parsons Machinery Co., November 6, 1923; 2468.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Vito Altamura and Luigi Quercia, January 22-February 7, 1924; 2484.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Walter H. and Homer T. Phillips, December 27, 1923-January 10, 1924; 2497.
  - Monga Land Co. and Louis Kotler, April 27, 1922; 2501.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John F. Holmes et ux, November 6, 1925; 2502.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Earnest J. Townes et ux, April 4, 1924; 2503.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Samuel D. McCloy, May 10, 1924-March 12, 1942; 2508.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. of Illinois and S. W. Straus & Co., May 7, 1924; 2523.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and George Demshar, July 23, 1924; 2530.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Stephen Herman et ux, September 5, 1924; 2538.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Carrie Geiger, April 24, 1924; 2546.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Joseph Mavrich, September 15, 1924; 2547.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Murray T. Fennell et ux, June 16, 1924; 2548.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Henry Stephenson, July 1, 1924-June 5, 1936; 2553.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Keystone Consolidated Publishing Co., October 14, 1924; 2557.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Angelo Tosi, October 16, 1924; 2563.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Burmid Oil and Gas Co., October 16, 1924-January 22, 1931; 2567.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Herman Potocnik, December 1, 1924; 2574.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Mercantile Bridge Co., October 15, 1924; 2577.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and John K. Tener, June 27, 1924-July 2, 1930; 2580.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Fairchance Lumber Co., January 23, 1925; 2583. (Box 67)
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and W. H. Williams, Trustee of Jacobs Creek Improvement Assn., January 31, 1925-February 6, 1930; 2591.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Frank F. Podrasky & John W. Podrasky, April 6, 1925; 2597.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Allen & Garcia Company, April 6, 1925; 2605.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Gussie C. Bolan -, April 30-May 8, 1925; 2608.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and H. F. Stark, May 29-December 15, 1925; 2612.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and A. G. Rothey, August 20, 1925; 2616.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Dominick Paladino et ux, August 13, 1925; 2621.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Evan I. Brown, October 3, 1925-January 22, 1926; 2622.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Nicholas Kiemes, September 17, 1925; 2623.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Angelo Nicolo et ux, September 28, 1925; 2625.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Thomas Watkins, July 9, 1925; 2634.
  - Surety Bonds for Duplicate Debenture Bonds, etc, December 15, 1921-September 2, 1925; 2636.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and James J. Boyle, June 13, 1925; 2639.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Dail A. Sloan et al, July 9, 1925; 2641.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Thomas Benich et ux, August 26-November 20, 1925; 2648.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Amelio Barney et ux, October 19, 1925; 2655.
  - Pittsburgh Coal Co. and Helen Mullen, October 19, 1925; 2656.